■
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译：小糯
■
校对：小糯      时间轴：今
后期：加森      总监：小糯
■
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第一集
■
什么
What?
不是吧
No!
琳  别再看那些逮捕名单了
Lin, you gotta stop reading the police blotter.
看完干生气
It just makes you mad.
这帮人干嘛偷球尔街的路牌啊
Why would someone steal the sign for Ball Street?
老天  这座小镇会变成怎样
Oh, God, what is this town coming to?
没救了
It's going to crap.
快跟我说说
Tell me about it.
今天还有人朝我的挡风玻璃扔冰淇淋呢
Somebody threw a snow cone at my windshield today.
我还以为是撞到彩虹了
I thought I hit a rainbow.
真是吓死人了
It was terrifying.
打住  我可不觉得我们小镇没救了
Oh, come on. I don't think this town is going to crap.
2:00了
That's my 2:00.
独眼蛇飞车党来了
The One Eyed Snakes motorcycle club.
他们的分会老大死得很诡异
Their chapter president died gruesomely.
葬礼由我包办
I'm doing the service.
怪不得你今天穿了条皮裤
That explains why you're wearing leather pants.
早就想晒晒这条裤子了
Been waiting forever to bust these out.
他看起来好像王子
He looks like Prince.
他看起来好像白萝卜王子
He looks like fat, white Prince.
伙计们  只许看不许摸哦
Look but don't touch, fellas.
天啊  他们几个是这里的霸主
Oh, no, these are the guys who took over the steps.
听说他们总是欺负小孩
I heard they pick on kids.
等等  我就是小孩
Wait. I'm a kid!
我说  咱们还是绕着走吧
Come on. Let's take the long way.
我才不怕高年级的呢
I'm not afraid of some high school kids.
看我的
Watch a "this".
喂  喂  此处禁止通行  [此处无法走动]
Hey, hey. You can't walk here.
哎哟喂  我走不动
Oh, my gosh, I can't walk here?
你看  真是奇了  我就是走得动
Oh, look, it's a miracle! I'm walking!
闭上你的臭嘴  白痴
Shut your butts, coconuts.
你说我走不动  可是我走得好着呢
But you said I couldn't, but I'm doing it.
把你的臭嘴给我闭上
But I want your butt to shut.
不如听我的臭嘴给你哼哼两句
Oh, listen to the hum of my butt.
听好了  抽死你  闭嘴  抽到你闭嘴
Oh, listen to this: clap, clap shut, clap it shut!
咱们回见
See you later!
我祝你生活霉满
Have a great life!
美满着呐
Oh, already having it!
-刚才好险啊  -就他们几个
- That was intense. - Those guys?
不过是满脸爆痘的小屁猫罢了
They're just little acne-covered kittens.
殡至如归
敝馆是您永远的家
霍尼・戴夫  愿你安息
上帝之所以赐你光环
是因为他没法让你戴着头盔升天
悼念仪式已经进行21分钟了
This memorial jam has been going on for 21 minutes.
要不要进入下一环节
I just wonder if I should fade it out.
这是霍尼・戴夫最喜欢的环节
This was Horny Dave's favorite jam.
继续
Keep it cranked.
这是他最喜欢的环节
Horny Dave's favorite jam?
这是我最喜欢的环节
This is my favorite jam.
继续  埃迪
Keep it cranked, Eddie!
天啊  别进来  别别别别  欢迎光临
Oh, God, don't come here, no, no, no, no. Welcome!
这儿有啤酒吗
You serve beer?
没...有
We... do not.
那是啥
What's that?
啤酒
That is beer.
抱歉  这儿有啤酒  我撒了谎
Sorry, we do. I lied.
向霍尼・戴夫致敬
Let's drink to Horny Dave.
敬霍尼・戴夫
To Horny Dave!
拼酒比赛的那个冠军  她怀孕了是吧
Um, the woman who won that drinking contest, she's pregnant, right?
据说已经几个月了
Well, they say in moderation.
老兄  他们对你的生活方式都没做评判呢
Hey, man, they don't judge your lifestyle,
你这只管收钱的老顽固
you buttoned-down pencil pusher.
什么
What?
抱歉  鲍鲍  这帮飞车党太有感染力了
Sorry, Bobby, this motorcycle thing's contagious.
我想晚上整辆自行车回来
I kinda want to go out and get a bike tonight.
挨家挨户捣乱  吼上一句"老不死的"
Hassle shopkeepers. "Hey, old man!" You know?
"你不认识我"
"You don't know me."
"我要用球棒敲烂你窗户砸碎你脑袋"
"I'll break your window and hit ya with a bat."
这主意不错  泰迪
Sounds like a great idea, Teddy.
说说而已
Ah, maybe not.
大概只会看看曲棍球比赛吧
Probably just watch a hockey game.
敬霍尼・戴夫  绝世英雄
To Horny Dave! A helluva man!
绝世朋友
A helluva friend!
绝世情人
A helluva lover!
又开始摔瓶子了
Uh, they broke more bottles.
看来我们汉堡店亮丽了好多
Whoa, looks like our restaurant just got a lot edgier.
希望还能迈进去脚
Hope I can still get in.
够呛
You probably can't.
二位等会见
I'll meet you guys after.
我喜欢你的帽子
I like your lid.
我喜欢你的马甲  还能穿真是奇迹
I like your vest. What's left of it.
是啊  它曾随我闯过鬼门关
Yep, these colors have been to hell and back.
一半留在那里回不来了
Part of 'em stayed in hell.
那些漂亮的徽章是什么
What are those pretty buttons?
这些补丁吗
Oh, these patches?
这个是纪念...胳肢过条子
Well, we got this one for... tickling a cop.
酷  那个呢
Cool! What's that one for?
纪念没有参加白人权力运动
For not being associated with the white power movement.
那个又是纪念什么
And what's that one for?
纪念吹了好多气球...
For blowing up a bunch of balloons...
给你们这样的小孩
for kids like you.
又是寻常的一天
Just an ordinary day.
在开心汉堡店的一天  是吧孩子们
Here at Bob's Burgers. Right, kids?
你们店不错  顺便告诉你  我是克里特
Nice place. I'm Critter, by the way.
我是鲍勃
Uh, Bob.
我是  飞车党的分会老大
Yeah, I'm the, uh, chapter president of these fellas.
之前是霍尼・戴夫  他死得好惨
Horny Dave was, till his grisly death.
那个  咱们还是别说了吧
Well, I'm sure you don't want to talk about it, so...
他开着卡车撞上沉船
Yeah, he got into a wreck with a semi, all right.
场面老火爆了
Real fiery.
等他被拉出来的时候
By the time they pulled him out,
他的老二  整根鸡鸡  全都焦了
his entire lower half, the horny half, was roasted.
所以这件本属于他的马甲才如此破烂
That's why Horny Dave's vest here is in tatters.
看着挺好的
Um, it looks nice.
-才不是呢  鲍勃  -的确不咋地
- No, it doesn't, Bob. - No, it doesn't.
这件马甲本该助我
This vest is supposed to make me look like
巩固老大地位  可是...
the unquestioned leader of this club, but instead I...
我看起来太二了
I just look foolish.
史代奇  玩阴的  就是这样
Whoa! Statch! Nasty Slim! Cool it!
看吧  霍尼・戴夫更有领导才能
See? Horny Dave was just a better leader.
如果兄弟打架  他会站出来说
If we were fighting, he'd come out and he'd say,
"咱来整点冰毒吧"
"Let's go cook some meth!"
于是我们开动  之后烦恼就忘得一干二净了
And we would, and we'd forget all our troubles.
听起来好温馨
That sounds nice.
我们也整点冰毒得了
Maybe we should cook meth.
我也想把烦恼忘光
I wanna forget my troubles.
上帝保佑这些冰毒
God bless this meth.
孩子们  进屋去
Kids, go inside.
那个是你老婆吧
So, uh, that's your old lady, huh?
是啊  叫她琳达  或者恐龙
Uh, yeah. She goes by Linda. Or Dragon.
哪个都行
Whichever.
那个是你老婆喽
So is that your old lady?
不  挡泥布是霍尼・戴夫的老婆
No, Mudflap was Horny Dave's.
这个女人很特别
She's a special woman.
她能用胸部起开啤酒瓶盖
She can open a beer with her boobs.
-我老婆可做不来  -这是一门艺术
- Mine can't do that. - It's an art.
天啊
Oh, my!
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
现在我想要胸部了
Now I want them.
这是加入飞车党的必要条件吗
Is that a requirement for being in the club?
这么简单就好了  加入我们帮派很难的
Wish it was that easy. Initiation was tough.
挡泥布把一个装碌淖岬闷ü瞿蛄
Mudflap beat the snot out of some poser
那天佐治亚州的梅肯市春光明媚
in Macon, Georgia one fine day in spring.
当晚就让她入党了
Got her colors that night.
-是秋天  -是春天
- It was fall. - It was spring.
因为我记得当时杜鹃花全都开了
I remember because the azaleas were in bloom.
杜鹃花
Ooh, azaleas.
梅肯市的杜鹃花漂亮极了
Oh, the azaleas are beautiful in Macon.
仅次于大力丸
Second only to their crank.
那美味的梅肯市大力丸
That sweet Macon crank.
-大力丸是什么  -冰毒的一种
- What's crank? - Like meth's dirty cousin.
我们正要制作冰毒呢
Oh, we're gonna cook meth.
该去睡觉了  宝贝们  快去吧
Okay, time for bed, sweeties. Come on.
我能不能拜托飞车党给我讲讲睡前故事
Can I bring a biker with me to tell me stories?
不行
No, you may not.
求求你嘛
Please...?
-就讲一个  -不行
- Just one! - No.
所有人都听好
All right, everybody.
这儿的啤酒已经被我们喝干了  咱们走
We drank the place dry. Let's ride!
来啊  小宝贝  骑上来
Come on, lil' sweetheart. Jump on back.
我敢肯定他们有特派司机
I'm sure they have designated drivers, so...
这点钱足够补偿你们的了
This should cover the damage.
抱歉上面沾了点血
Sorry there's blood on some of it.
还有一件事  给
Oh, one last thing. Here.
这是什么
What's this?
我们欠你一个人情
Means we owe you one.
贴在橱窗上  保证没人敢碰你
Put it in your window. Nobody will mess with you.
除了秃鹰王
Uh, except maybe the Buzzard Kings.
他们也许会往这里扔燃烧弹
They might throw a Molotov cocktail in here.
出事就给我打电话
You call me if they do.
不不不  贴在窗户上
Uh! No, no, no. Right in the window.
现在  我们有保护伞了
So, we've got this now.
我们又要从这儿过了
Uh-oh, we're crossing paths again.
We're crossing paths!
还记得我跟你说过"此路不通"么
Hey, remember when I told you not to come around here?
记不太清了  过去的事我一向健忘
Guess not. I'm not so good with history.
我也是
Me, neither!
虽然我历史很好
I'm pretty good at history,
但是数学却很糟糕
but I have some problems with math.
我会透视未来
Well, I'm taking a course in the future.
你知道等下会发生什么吗
You know what happens in the future?
我们会从你身边走过
We walk right past you.
我只是不想放学后的娱乐时间
Uh! I just want no little kids around me
还看到你们这群小屁孩
when I'm decompressing after school.
我正在努力创造一个轻松的氛围
I'm trying to create a relaxed environment,
我想让我的朋友感到舒服自在
I'm making my friends feel comfortable,
结果你们这几个臭屁孩子不请自来
and then you come by with all this attitude!
你可千万别惹我老妹
Hey, you don't want to mess with my sister.
她会让你好多年都抬不起头
She'll wear down your self-esteem over a period of years.
闭嘴  四眼妹
Shut up, four-eyes.
我在跟四耳妹说话
I'm talking to four-ears.
我的四只耳朵可听不见你说话
With four ears, I can ignore you twice as hard.
什么什么  什么什么
What, what? What, what?
你已经把我逼到忍无可忍了
You've pushed me to the point of break.
我要没收这只帽子
I'm confiscating these.
回见
Laters!
这他妈什么鸟事
What just frigging happened?!
我不禁注意到
So, I couldn't help notice
某人的兔耳帽不见了
someone doesn't have their bunny ears on.
我知道说我呢  行吗
Ha-ha! I know, right?
很久没看到你不戴帽子的样...
It's, uh, been a pretty long time since we've seen you without your...
很久了  很...久了
Too long! Too... long!
好吧
Okay.
露易丝  也许告诉爸妈实话你会感觉好点
Louise, maybe you'd feel better if you told mom and dad...
告诉他们我有多快乐吗
How happy I am?
老妈  来击个掌
Mom, up high.
-我也要  -好咧  老哥
- I'll take one. - You got it, bro!
鲍鲍  要不我去跟她谈谈
Do you think I should go talk to her, Bobby?
免了吧
No, you shouldn't!
我很好  好得不得了
I'm great! Just fantastic!
再等等吧
Uh, maybe wait.
你今天怎么没戴兔耳帽
You're not wearing your ears today.
还是帽子隐形了
Or are they invisible?
隐形了
Invisible?!
你这想法是哪来的
Where do you come up with this stuff?
你的心灵太美好了
Your mind is so beautiful!
接受现实吧
Yeah, take it in!
露易丝  怎么没戴兔耳帽呢
Whoa, Louise, not wearing your bunny ears?
这事很严重
This is big.
很多问题要讨论  很多情绪要处理
Lots of issues to discuss, feelings to process.
好啊  跟我说说啊  福旺德先生
Oh, yeah, tell me about it, Mr. Frond!
我正要处理一场情绪风暴
I am processing up a storm,
正好缺个搭档陪我
but I could really use a processing-partner!
-是我吗  -就是你  去你办公室  五分钟
- Me?! - Great idea! Your office? Five minutes?
我走了
I'm out of here.
我要去台阶那里找那个傻乱回我的帽子
I'm gonna wait for that punk at the steps and get my ears back.
我们陪你去
We'll come with you.
不用  你们回家不要跟爸妈说实话
No. You guys go home and lie to mom and dad.
好的  我擅长撒谎  不擅长打架
Good. I'm a liar, not a fighter.
-露易丝  等等  -怎么了
- Louise, wait. - What?
要不要等你一起吃晚饭
You want us to keep your dinner warm?
好啊  等着我
Yeah. Real warm.
哎哟  你戴着我的帽子呐
Hello, I see you're wearing my ears.
好像有点戴偏了
Oh, they're off-center a smidge.
我来给你...
Let me just...
想得美  屁孩
Nice try, kid.
好吧  我们都是道儿上的
Fine. We're all young professionals here.
我叫露易丝  我还不知道你的名字呢
I'm Louise, by the way. I don't think I got your name.
洛根
Logan.
Logan...
我兜里这是什么呀
what's this in my pocket?
一二三四五六
Oh, one, two, three, four, five, six,
七八九美元  买那只帽子
seven, eight, nine dollars for the hat.
我可不是什么便宜的妓女
You can't buy me like a cheap sex lady!
太慢了  太矮了
Too slow, down low.
你不如重上一遍计划学校
Why don't you go back to plan-school
因为你看起来非常需要重新塑造
because looks like you need a better one.
你怎么不去上计划学校呢
Why don't you go to plan-school?!
-你怎么不去  -你怎么不去
- Why don't you? - Why don't you?
- No, you, why don't you? - Why don't you?!
-你怎么不去  -你怎么不去
- No, why don't you? - Why don't you?!
我们该怎么处理这张卡片
What do we do with this card?
要拿下来吗  看着好诡异
Take it down? It's creepy.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
还记得你撤掉那只筹款罐的事吗
Remember when you took down that charity jar?
你也见识到那些胸癌患者有多愤怒了
You saw how pissed those breast cancer people got.
你好  父亲母亲
Hey, parentals.
露易丝呢
Where's Louise?
-买帽子去了  -买帽子去了
- Hat shopping? - Shopping for hats.
可以理解
Huh, that makes sense.
看来露易丝得转变一下风格了
I guess Louise needs to transition from bunny ears to something.
这就好比辅助车轮
Like training wheels.
就像上次我们让吉恩养鱼
Like when we got a fish for Gene
好看看他是否有责任心养狗
to prove he was responsible enough to get a dog.
-事实证明我没有  -可怜的鱼儿
- I was not. - That poor fish.
那么  我们到底去哪
So, where are we going?
我的时间充裕着呢
My calendar is wide open.
是啊  我到家了
Yeah, well, uh, I'm home now.
那你就接着跑吧  小狗狗
So, run along, little doggie.
不  是我们到家了
No, we're home now.
除非我夺回帽子
Until I get those ears back,
否则你去哪  我去哪
wherever you go, I go.
去上学吗  洛根  我也去
Going to school, Logan? I'll join you.
走吧
Let's do it.
休想
Nope.
洛根  洛根  洛根  洛根  你都干嘛
Logan, Logan, Logan, Logan. What do you do?
赫克斯利高中
你会在上课前先去更衣柜
You go to your locker before you go to class
还是直接上课  还是去尿尿
or you go to class? Gotta pee?
一般都是什么行程
What's the routine here?
你知道的  我要在男厕尿尿
You know, I could pee... in the boys' room.
怎么  你以为我不会进去么
Well, you think I won't go in there?
我是不会放弃的  洛根
I'm not giving up, Logan.
我要拖垮你
I will wear you down.
因为这顶帽子  我约到了舞会的女伴
I got a prom date because of these ears.
模拟测试也考了个高分
My practice SAT scores went up.
我也不会放弃的
I'm not giving up, either.
这里臭死了
Whoo! It stinks in here.
欢迎吸取美味
Welcome to boys' smell.
洛根  我喜欢你这兔耳
Logan! I like your bunny ears.
谢了  莎娜雅
Thanks, Shanaya.
那不是他的兔耳
They're not his ears!
这么快就要离开真是遗憾啊
Oh, sorry you had to leave so soon!
别怪我没跟你好商好量  洛根
Let the record show that I tried to reason with you, Logan!
现在开始我要动武了
Now I have to go nuclear!
有事吗
Can I help you?
真希望我没有打扰你们用餐  女士
I hope I'm not interrupting dinner, ma'am,
可是你的儿子  他偷了我的东西
but your son... he stole something of mine.
洛根
Logan!
你偷了这个女孩的兔耳帽
You took this girl's bunny ears?
本来我不想告状的  是你逼得我没有选择
I didn't want to tattle, but you left me no choice.
是啊  是我偷的
Yeah. I took 'em.
还给她  马上
Return them. Now.
已经扔了
I threw 'em away.
我说过  你要不回去的
I told you you'd never get 'em back.
你在说谎
Bull, you threw them away.
不信就去搜我房间
Search my room.
洛根
Ugh, Logan.
对不起  我给你开张支票吧  20美元怎么样
Sorry, I'll write you a check. $20?
20有点多啊  亲爱的
20 seems a bit high, honey.
天啊汤姆  现在不是时候
Oh, God, Tom. Not now!
你把帽子扔哪了
Where did you throw them away?
潘秋玉米卷那里
Pancho's Tacos.
具体哪家店  洛根  潘秋是连锁店
Which one, Logan? It's a chain!
生意好的那家  就在河岸附近
The good one. The one on riverside.
潘秋玉米卷
垃圾箱
孩子  你要找的东西已经被烧了
Uh, kid, what you're looking for was incinerated.
没了
It's gone.
化成灰烬了  抱歉
Burned up. Sorry.
不
No!
我要复仇
Revenge.
-是这个吗  -不是
- Is this it? - No!
-是这个吗  -是两只粉色兔耳
- Are these it? - It's pink with ears.
-没有了  -是顶帽子
- Oh, then they're gone. - It's a hat.
没了  那就是没了
No. Then they're gone.
我还记得这顶帽子
Hey, I remember this hat.
本来应该属于我的  记得吗
It was gonna be my thing. Remember?
我本可以赢到的  是吧
I could pull this off. Right?
是啊  你当然能赢了
Um... Yeah, of course you can!
你回来了  我的宝贝女儿
There she is, my little big girl.
蒂娜和吉恩跟我们说你去市场
Tina and Gene told us you were in the market
淘转型帽子去了
for an in-between hat,
所以我们从衣柜里拿了几顶出来
so we dug some out of the closet.
也许这顶不行  也许你不想要
Maybe not this one. You probably don't want this one.
你们几个真是太体贴了
How thoughtful of you all,
可我不需要帽子完善自我
but I don't need a hat to complete me.
我只需要我自己  我自己
I'm all I need. Just me.
这话我一直在对你说
That's what I keep telling you.
晚安  琳达
Good night, Linda.
谢谢你们想着我
Thank you for thinking about me.
别客气
You're welcome.
我需要的只是那顶帽子
All I need is that hat!
这是我的
Mine!
看看谁来了
Look who it is.
你怎么不戴猪耳帽呢  和你说话风格多配啊
Surprised you don't have pig ears on, the way you squeal.
我问你  你听力如何
Question. How's your hearing?
挺好的  怎么了
Uh, pretty good. Why?
那么  你能听见这个声音吧
Well, then I guess you can hear that.
这是复仇之音
That's the sound of revenge.
你拿了本不属于你的东西
For taking that which wasn't yours,
所以我召集独眼蛇前来
I have summoned the wrath of the One Eyed Snakes!
地狱也不曾有过...
Hell hath no fury like...
先熄会儿火
Kill the bikes for a second!
谢谢
Thank you.
地狱也不曾有过...
Hell hath no fury...
这部分你听到了吗
Did you hear that part? About hell?
听到了
Yeah, I think so.
很好  因为这句话的后半句是
Good. Cause the rest of it is,
"地狱也不曾有过如此深重的怨念  洛根"
"Hell hath no fury like I do, Logan!"
你抢走我的兔耳帽  又把它扔了
You took my ears and threw them away.
现在这些人
And now these guys
将要割掉你的耳朵  然后扔掉
are going to take your ears and throw them away.
什么
What?
天啊
Oh, boy.
我还是捂着点眼睛吧
I'm going to watch through my fingers.
不  不要  我还是不看了吧
No, I'm not. I'm going to look away.
看来以后我们得低调一阵子了
I think we're gonna have to lay low for a little while after this.
天啊  不要割掉我的耳朵
Oh, God, don't cut my ears off!
我讨厌衬衫标签在外面支着
I hate when shirt tags stick out.
给给给给  帽子我没扔
Here, here, here, here! I never threw them out, okay?
对不起
I'm so sorry!
我的...我的兔耳帽
My... My ears.
求你不要割掉我的耳朵
Please don't cut off my ears!
不要割掉
Leave 'em where they are.
它们  它们在这儿挺好的
They... They look good in that position.
我能看了吗
Can I look yet?
先别  能看的时候我会告诉你的
Nee-ya... I'll let you know.
我的手上一股洋葱味儿  真好闻
My hands smell like onions. It's nice.
别再惹我们了  洛根
Don't ever mess with us again, Logan.
马上给我滚
Now, get the hell outta here!
就是这样  就是这样
Yeah! That's how you do it! That's how you do it!
不不不不  我们刚刚收拾好
No, no, no, no, we just got the place back together.
欢迎回来  伙计们  你们好吗
Welcome back, fellas. How are you?
孩子们
Kids?
怎么回事
What's going on?
露易丝  你又戴上兔耳帽了
Louise, you're wearing your ears again.
帽子被一个小孩偷走了
Yeah, some kids stole 'em
是这些兄弟夺回来的
and these mamma-jammas got 'em back!
兄弟  什么  你的帽子被偷了
Mamma-jammas, what? Your ears were stolen?
是的  我用了那张独眼蛇保护卡
Yup. I cashed in the card the One Eyed Snakes gave us.
很高兴再次简单你  鲍勃  帽子不错
Good to see you again, Bob. Nice hat.
真的吗  你真的这么想吗
Ah, really? Yeah, you think so?
我跟他们说  来店里随便吃随便喝
Oh, and I told them food and drinks are on the house.
不  他们...这...不...
No. They... That's... No. I don't think that's...
听到了吗  尽情疯吧
Ya hear that, boys? Go crazy!
-好耶  -不  不  不不不
- All right! - No. No. No, no, no.
好耶  疯起来
All right, let's go crazy.
别这样
Please don't go crazy.
这帮人真嗨啊
They really got crazy.
诸位有事吗
Um, can I help you folks?
有
Yes.
我们是小区里的家长
We are parents in this community,
我们正处在一个危险肮脏的飞车酒馆
and we're marching on your filthy, dangerous biker bar.
这里不是飞车酒馆
We're not a biker bar.
这帮飞车党正喝着你的啤酒
You are serving beer to a ton of bikers.
汤姆  你先别说
Tom, please.
这间飞车酒吧使得我们小镇日渐衰败
This biker bar is the reason our town is going down the tubes.
我们绝不允许暴力存在  影响我们的孩子
And we will not allow violence against our children to continue.
暴力
Violence!
暴力  什么暴力
Violence? What violence?
这些飞车党想要割掉我的耳朵
Those bikers wanted to cut off my ears.
老天
Oh, God.
冷静一下  我们不会割掉谁的耳朵
Ah, calm down, we weren't gonna cut off any ears.
别听他的  他会的
Don't listen to him. He would have.
-不  我不会  -是的  你会
- No, I wouldn't. - Yeah, you would.
我告诉你  我不会
I'm tellin' ya, I would not...
我说你会
I think you would have.
你根本不了解我
You don't know my mind!
听着  我只是教训了一下这些小坏蛋罢了
You see, I was just teaching these little bullies a lesson.
就是这个臭小子欺负我们家露易丝吧
So this is the brat who picked on my Louise, huh?
我可告诉你  普利斯夫人
Let me tell you something, Miss Priss.
-琳  -你别管
- Lin... - No. I got this.
小镇的隐患不是这帮飞车党  而是你家小孩
These bikers aren't the problem in this town; it's your kids.
他们就是一群野兽
They're a bunch of animals.
是啊夫人  管好你们家孩子
Yeah, lady! Control your kids.
是你们家小孩不听管教吧
Oh, it is your kids who cannot be controlled.
没错  我已经失控了
She's right. I'm out of control.
你怎么不去电话亭放屁呢
Oh, why don't you go fart in a phone booth!
好了  琳  冷静冷静
All right, Lin, calm down.
跟这个贱人说什么冷静
You tell this hussy to calm down.
是啊  冷静冷静  贱人
Yeah, calm it, hussy!
别叫我老婆贱人
Do not call my wife a whore.
我才不要呢
Oh, I will not calm it.
琳  别...
Lin, stop...
别这样
Don't do this...
抓她胸部  老妈
Pull out her highlights, mom.
好了好了  大家都冷静冷静
All right, all right, everybody just calm down.
快捡起来  然后道歉  然后离开
Pick that up, apologize and leave.
好吗  我是为你好
Please. For your own good.
我才不会做这种事呢
I will do no such thing.
让你走你不走
Shoulda left when you coulda left.
伙计们  有家伙的抄家伙
Everyone who's got a knife, grab it!
让我们决一死战
It's a fight to the death!
你不能跟他们动手  克里特
Hey, hey, you can't fight these people, Critter.
你会...你会杀了他们的
You'll... You'll destroy them.
只要有人招惹独眼蛇兄弟
When somebody messes with the One Eyed Snake's colors,
他就要付出代价
they gotta pay.
箭在弦上  我没得选
My leadership's on the line. I got no choice.
我们得放点血出来
We gotta hurt these people.
霍尼・戴夫会带着手下殴打白领父母吗
Would Horny Dave have his men beat up some white collar parents?
霍尼・戴夫已经死了
Horny Dave is dead.
好了  开始吧  动手
All right, it's going on now, here it goes.
不过是虚张声势罢了
They're just bluffing.
我们独眼蛇从不虚张声势
The One Eyed Snakes don't bluff.
贝尔彻家小孩也从不虚张声势
Neither do the Belcher kids!
除了我们虚张声势的时候
Except when we do.
好  让我们继续喊吧
Yeah! Let's keep shouting stuff!
去他的真实想法
Screw inside voices!
好了  我要报警了
Okay, I'm calling the police.
不要
No!
我的手机
My running mix!
说够了没有  开打...
Oh, enough talk. Let's kick...
挡泥布  你还好吗
Mudflap, are you okay?
没事  只是宫缩罢了  咱...
I'm fine, it was just a contraction. Let's...
宫缩
Contraction?
你快要生了吗
You're in labor?
等我们动完手再生
Hold that kid in till we're done!
我试试  不行了
I'll try. No, I can't.
我要生了  我要生了
This baby's coming. Oh, this baby's coming.
我去叫救护车
I'll call an ambulance.
我是医生
I'm a doctor.
-快他妈的过来  -好
- Well, then get the hell over here! - All right.
快下去看看情况  医生
Get under the hood and check the oil, doc.
好的  好好
Okay. Okay, okay.
宫缩多久一次
Uh, how far apart are the contractions?
-没多久  -好了
- They are not. - Oh! Wow. Okay.
孩子就要出来了
This baby is coming now.
马上就要到我手上了
Like right into my hand.
保持呼吸
Don't forget to breathe.
要不要给你拿个木勺子咬着
Do you want me to get you a wooden spoon to bite on?
别拿勺子了  给我威士忌
Oh, forget the spoon. Get me whiskey.
威士忌可能...
Um, I'm not sure whiskey is...
我高尔夫球袋里有瓶酒
I have a flask in my golf bag.
我这里也有一瓶  哪去了
Yeah, I got one here, somewhere...
我有笑气筒
I got some whip-its.
给  喝我的吧
Here. Take mine.
等一下
Hold on a sec.
很好  你做得很棒
Okay, you're doing great.
你叫什么
Uh, what's your name?
挡泥布
Mudflap.
挡泥布  我奶奶也叫这名字
Oh, Mudflap, uh... That was my grandmother's name.
-真的吗  -不  不
- Really? - No, no.
你的名字是卡车的一个肮脏部件
You're named after a dirty part of a truck.
好了  保持呼吸
Okay, keep breathing.
好
Okay.
准备好  用力
And... ready... push!
就当是卤汁面条好了
Just pretend it's lasagna.
真不知道挡泥布不打硬脊膜外麻醉要怎么生
I don't know how Mudflap's doing this without an epidural.
如果当初生洛根时不打那针的话
If I didn't have one with Logan?
快跟我说说
Ugh, tell me about it.
那两个  小菜一碟
Those two? Piece of cake.
那一个  大菜一缸
That one? A whole cake.
很抱歉我们家洛根欺负你们家孩子
I'm sorry my Logan picked on your kids.
很抱歉我们家孩子利用飞车党吓唬你们家洛根
Hey. I'm sorry my kids had bikers threaten to cut your kid's ears off.
来帮我把她的双腿抬高  就像这样
I need you guys to hold up her knees, just like this...
好了  我看到头了
Okay. I see the head.
我看到了  是颗头
Oh, I looked. That's a head.
希望那是颗头
I hope that's a head.
我不应该看的  可是我看了
I shouldn't have looked. I looked.
再用用力  挡泥布
One more big push, Mudflap!
好
Okay!
出来了
Here it comes!
他又不用擦桌子
Not it to clean the table.
是个男孩  赤身裸体的
It's a boy. Barely.
挡泥布  你想让在场的哪位剪断脐带
Mudflap, is there someone you'd like to cut the cord?
他的爸爸
His daddy.
可是霍尼・戴夫已经死了啊
But Horny Dave's dead.
不  克里特  霍尼・戴夫95年就做过结扎手术了
No, Critter, Horny Dave had a vasectomy in '95.
-来  -你在说什么  你这女人
- Come here. - What are you saying, woman?
这孩子是你的
This baby's yours.
我还是不懂
I still don't understand.
克里特  我们上过床  我被你弄得晕了过去
Critter, we had sex and you knocked me up...
慢着  慢着
Slow down! Slow down!
这孩子是你的
This baby is your spawn.
等一下  什么意思
Wait a minute, what do you mean?
你成爸爸了
You're a daddy.
什么时候开始的
From when?
九个月前
Sometimes
你睡过的那个女人
the one you slept with nine months ago
一直在你左右
was right in front of you all along.
挡泥布
Oh, Mudflap.
我来割断脐带
Give me that cord.
好了  现在可以开打了吧
Okay, are we gonna have the fight now? Or...
露易丝  别打了
Louise, there's gonna be no fight.
这小家伙比霍尼・戴夫还有劲儿
This little kid squashed a beef better than Horny Dave ever did.
我的儿子  怎么样
My boy. How about that?
给  克里车
Here, Creature.
克里特
Critter.
对  把它给孩子盖上吧
Right. Maybe you could use it as a baby blanket.
谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
谢谢帮忙  医生
And thanks for getting your hands dirty, doc.
没事儿
No problem.
小区父母帮助飞车党成为父母
Aw. Parents helping bikers who are now parents.
我们小镇虽然存在问题
See, our town has its problems.
但并不代表我们小镇会垮掉
But it doesn't mean it's going in the crapper.
要想拥有和睦的邻里关系
It just means if we want to be a better neighborhood,
我们就要友好地对待彼此
we have to be better neighbors to each other.
-拉倒吧  -好了露易丝  来
- Stinks! - Okay, Louise, come on.
多谢
Thanks a lot.
你很勇敢
You were very brave.
你能自己挺身而出
You stood up for yourself,
向危险的飞车党求助
got help from dangerous bikers,
期间没有兔耳帽相伴
all without your ears.
也许你不再需要它了呢
Maybe you don't need them anymore.
也许吧
Maybe.
我知道也许有人比我更需要它
And maybe I know someone who needs them more than me.
我知道  这顶帽子对你意义非凡  洛根
Look, these ears mean a lot to you, Logan,
不如给你吧
so how about you keep 'em?
-真的吗  -给我歇菜
- Really? - No frigging way!
我逗你玩呢  你这白痴
I was just messing with you, you idiot!
欢迎回家  兔耳帽  来喝一杯吧
Welcome home, ears. Let's get you a beer.
老爸  两杯啤酒
Dad, two beers.
不行
No.
是给兔耳帽喝的
They're for my ears!